A Guide to the Equal Suffrage League of Virginia records, 1908-1938
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Equal Suffrage League of Virginia records, 1908-1938
The Library of Virginia
22002
13.33 cu. ft. and 31 boxes
Equal Suffrage League of Virginia
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Ida Mae Thompson, Richmond, Virginia.
Historical Information
The Equal Suffrage League of Virginia was organized in 1909 in Richmond, Virginia. Its primary purpose was to publicize and propagandize women's issues in the state, with the goal to win the political vote. Virginia was one of the six states which did not ratify the amendment. The final board meeting of the Equal Suffrage League was on November 8, 1920, and it became the League of Women Voters on November 10, 1920.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1909-1938, of the Equal Suffrage League of Virginia, including correspondence, organization records for both the Equal Suffrage League and the League of Women Voters, printed materials, "Votes for Women" buttons, and postcards.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
I: Correspondence, 1909-1933
II: Equal Suffrage League of Virginia records
III: National American Woman Suffrage Association (NAWSA)
IV: League of Women Voters of Virginia
V: National League of Women Voters
VI: General and Miscellaneous files
VII: Ephemera
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
See also League of Women Voters of Virginia records, 1920-2011 (LVA accession 39487).
Contents List
- Series I: Correspondence, 1909-1933., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 1-4)
  Correspondence, 1909-1933, contains letters, postcards, telegrams, and other papers consisting of correspondence between officers of the Equal Suffrage League of Virginia, its local chapters, and the National American Woman Suffrage Association, as well as other organizations and individuals. Also includes some correspondence relating to the League of Women Voters at the state, local, and national levels. Includes professional and personal correspondence of Ida Mae Thompson, Jessie Townsend, Alice M. Tyler, and others.
  - Correspondence, 1909 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, 1910 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1912 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, March 1912 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, April 1912 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, May 1912 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, June-August 1912 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, September 1912 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, October 1912 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, November, no month 1912 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, January-August 1913 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1913 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, November-December, no month 1913 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, January-March 1914 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, April-July 1914 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, August-October 1914 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, November-December, no month 1914 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, January 1915 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, February 1915 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1915 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, May 1915 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, June 1915 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, July-August 1915 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, September-October 1915 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, November-December, no month 1915 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, January 1916 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, February 1916 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, March 1916 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, April 1916 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, May 1916 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, June 1916 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, July 1916 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, August 1916 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, September 1916 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, October 1916 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, November-December, no month 1916 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1917 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, March-June 1917 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, July 1917 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, August-December 1917 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, January-May 1918 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, June-October 1918 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence, November 1918 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence, December 1918 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1919 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence, March-April 1919 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Correspondence, May-June 1919 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence, July 1919 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence, August 1919 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, September 1919 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, October 1919 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, November 1919 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, December 1919 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, no month 1919 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, January 1920 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, February 1920 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, April-June 1920 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, July-September 1920 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1920 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, no month 1920 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, January-February 1921 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence, March-May 1921 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, June-September 1921 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, October-December 1921 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence, 1923 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence, 1924 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence, 1926 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1927 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1928 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence, 1929 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence, 1931 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence, 1932 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence, 1933 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, undated (folder 1 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, undated (folder 2 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, undated (folder 3 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence, undated (folder 4 of 4) (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Ida Mae Thompson papers (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Jessie Townsend papers (folder 1 of 2) (see also Box 13, Folders 16-18; Box 20, Folders 11, 25) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Jessie Townsend papers (folder 2 of 2) (see also Box 13, Folders 16-18; Box 20, Folders 11, 25) (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Jessie Townsend correspondence (non-suffrage) (see also Box 13, Folders 16-18, Box 20, Folders 11, 25) (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Alice M. Tyler correspondence (non-suffrage) (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Correspondence (non-suffrage)--Miss Neely; Ella G. Agnew; Adele Clark and Nora Houston (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Series II: Equal Suffrage League of Virginia., Extent: 11 boxes. (Box 5-15)
  Equal Suffrage League of Virginia records contain state league constitution; yearbooks; meeting minutes; state convention programs; reports; resolutions; financial records; issues of the Virginia Suffrage News; news bulletins; booklets, pamphlets, broadsides, and flyers; calling cards, pledge cards; and membership lists. Series also contains information on the Virginia General Assembly, as well as records from local chapters throughout Virginia.
  - State League records., 7 boxes (Box 5-11)
    - Constitution, drafts, etc. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Yearbooks, 1910, 1916 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Meeting minutes, 1909-1910 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Meeting minutes, 1911 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Meeting minutes, 1912 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Meeting minutes, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Executive council/state board meeting minutes, 1914-1919 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - State convention minutes; executive board minutes, 1914; 7 November 1914 and 14 October 1915 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Meeting agendas, undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Memoranda books, 1916-1917 (Edith C. Cowles) (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Memoranda books, 1916-1919 (Edith C. Cowles) (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Annual meeting, 1910 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Third state convention, 1913 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Fourth state convention, 1914 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Fifth state convention, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - State convention register, 1915 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Sixth state convention, 1916 (program, delegate roster) (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Sixth state convention, 1916 (minutes, report) (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Seventh state convention, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Registration for seventh state convention; also organization of State League of Women Voters, 1917; 1920 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Eighth state convention, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Reports on state convention, 1911-1912 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - State convention delegates, 1914-1919, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Presidential survey, state yearbook, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Executive secretary reports (includes Richmond city league), 1915-1920 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Headquarters reports (includes Richmond city league), 1912-1916 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Headquarters reports (includes Richmond city league), 1917-1920 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1912-1919 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Officers and committees, 1916-1917, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Credentials committee, undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Election committee reports, 1916-1917, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Committee on nominations, ca. 1914-1916 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Political study and research, 1916, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Report of the committee on resolutions, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - State congressional committee, 1916-1917 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Committees reports, 1912, undated (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous reports and related papers (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Legislative committee, 1914 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Legislative committee--General Assembly, 1914 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Legislative committee--General Assembly, 1916 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Legislative committee, 1917 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Legislative committee--General Assembly, 1918 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Legislative committee, [1919] (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Legislative committee--General Assembly, 1919 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Legislative committee, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Legislative committee, [1920] (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Legislative committee--General Assembly, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Legislative committee--General Assembly, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Legislative committee--Federal amendment file, 1920 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Legislative committee--Presidential suffrage file, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Legislative committee--U.S. Senate vote list (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Legislative committee--General Assembly, undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Annual reports to National American Woman Suffrage Association (NAWSA), 1912-1919, [1920?] (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Report on NAWSA, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Reports to NAWSA, 1910-1918 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - State pledges to NAWSA, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Resolutions, 1912-1914 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Resolutions, 1915 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Resolutions, 1917, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - National Woman Suffrage Publishing Company, 1917-1919 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Agreements, contracts, 1912, 1917, undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Receipts, etc., 1912-1921, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Taxes, 1912 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Expense account: Eudora W. Ramsay (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Expense account: Adele Clark, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Virginia Suffrage News, 1914 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - News Bulletins, 1914-1915 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - News Bulletins, 1916 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - News Bulletins, 1917 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - News Bulletins, 1918 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - News Bulletins, 1919 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - News Bulletins, 1920 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - News Bulletins, undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Booklets: Facts vs. Fallacies, State Laws Concerning Women, The Subjection of Women According to St. Paul (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Pamphlets: Lucy R. Mason (The Divine Discontent, The Religious and Social Aspect of the Suffrage Movement) and Mary Johnston (The Reason Why, The Status of Women) (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Pamphlets: Equal Suffrage League of Virginia (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Pamphlets: Virginia law and Government (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Pamphlets: General (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Broadsides (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Broadsides and flyers (folder 1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Broadsides and flyers (folder 2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Publications and broadsides drafts (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Flyers drafts (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Press releases, 1911-1920 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Press releases, undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - New articles on the league and on suffrage, 1913-1916 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Letters to the Editor, 1913, 1918, 1920 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Ballots for officers, 1916, undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Biographical sketches (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Deeds of lease, 13 June 1913, 1 September 1917 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Questionnaire/interview responses on suffrage question, General Assembly, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Speeches (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Drafts of essays, speeches, reports, and correspondence (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - How the Vote Was Won--play program, 17 February 1914 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - World War papers, 1917-1918, 1921 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - History--drafts (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - History--correspondence, 1919-1922 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Draft of proposed legislation/amendment (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - Calling cards and announcements (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous notes (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Petitions, blank (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Stationery, blank (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Envelopes, blank (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Scrapbook, 1914-1916 (Box 9)
    - Scrapbook, 1916-1919 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Scrapbook, 1917-1919 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Scrapbook, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Scrapbook--leadership and history (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Scrapbook--loose items (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Scrapbook--cover only (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Pledges, 1915-1917, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Pledges, 1915, 1919, undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Pledges, undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Pledge cards, 1915 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Pledges (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Membership lists: Counties A-E, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Membership lists: Counties F-H, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Membership lists: Counties I-M, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Membership lists: Counties N-W, 1919 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Membership lists: various locations, 1912, 1916, undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Members: men, 1911 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Membership cards, 1915, undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Presidents of local leagues (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Petitions: Albemarle County (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Petitions: Alexandria (folder 1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Petitions: Alexandria (folder 2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Petitions: Alleghany County (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Petitions: Augusta County (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Petitions: Chesterfield County (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Petitions: Clarke County (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Petitions: Essex County (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Petitions: Fluvanna County (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Petitions: Grayson County (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Petitions: Greensville County (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Petitions: Hampto (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Petitions: King George County (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Petitions: King Wiiliam County (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Petitions: Lancaster County (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Petitions: Mecklenburg County (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Petitions: Nansemond County (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Petitions: Nottoway County (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - Petitions: Powhatan County (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - Petitions: Prince William County (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Petitions: Princess Anne County (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Petitions: Richmond Anne County (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Petitions: Rockbridge County (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Petitions: Southampton County (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Petitions: Sussex County (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Petitions: Westmoreland County (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Petitions: miscellaneous (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Index cards referencing members of the General Assembly, 1920 (Box 11)
  - Local Chapters., 4 boxes (Box 12-15)
    - Accomac County (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Albemarle County (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Albemarle County--University (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Alleghany County (includes some Clifton Forge) (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Amelia County (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Amherst County (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Appomattox County (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Arlington County (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Bath County (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Bedford County (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Botetourt County (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Brunswick County (see also Greensville County) (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Buckingham County (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Campbell County (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Caroline County (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Carroll County (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Charles City County (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Charlotte County (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Chesterfield County (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Clarke County (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Clifton Forge (see also Alleghany County) (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Culpeper County (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Cumberland County (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Danville (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Essex County (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Fairfax County (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Fauquier County (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Fauquier County--Warrenton (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Floyd County (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Fluvanna County (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Franklin County (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Gloucester County (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Fredericksburg (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Giles County (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Goochland County (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Grayson County (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Greensville County (includes some Brunswick County) (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Halifax County (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Hampton (see also Newport News) (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Hanover County (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Henrico County (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Henrico County--Westhampton College (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Henry County (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Henry County--Martinsville (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Highland County (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Isle of Wight County (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - James City County (see also Williamsburg) (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - King George County (also King and Queen County) (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - King William County (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Lancaster County (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Lancaster County--Irvington (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Loudoun County (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Louisa County (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Lunenburg County (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Lynchburg (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Lynchburg--Randolph-Macon Woman's College (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Mecklenburg County (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Mecklenburg County--Boydton (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Mecklenburg County--Clarksville (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Mecklenburg County--South Hill (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Middlesex County--Saluda (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Middlesex County--Urbanna (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Montgomery County (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Montgomery County--Shawsville (Box 12, Folder 64)
    - Nelson County (Box 12, Folder 65)
    - New Kent County (Box 12, Folder 66)
    - Newport News (see also Hampton) (Box 12, Folder 67)
    - Newport News treasurer's book, 1913-1917 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Norfolk--correspondence about formation, 1936 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Norfolk--minutes, November 1912, November 1914-January 1915 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Norfolk--records, executive board, January-March 1913, October 1915-November 1916 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Norfolk--minutes, 1914-1915, no year (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Norfolk--orders of the day (agendas), 1913-1915, 1917 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Norfolk--yearly reports, 1913-1916 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Norfolk--secretary's book, February 1912-January 1913 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Norfolk--recording secretary's book, January 1913-January 1914 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Norfolk--treasurer's book, 1915-1919 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Norfolk--Account book, 1915 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Norfolk--library (literary committee), February 1914 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Norfolk--meetings, programs (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Norfolk--membership list, undated (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Norfolk--precinct lists, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Norfolk--Your Girl and Mine (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Norfolk--Jessie Townsend correspondence, undated (see also Box 4, Folders 21-23; Box 20, Folders 11, 25) (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Norfolk--Jessie Townsend personal papers, notes drafts (folder 1 of 2) (see also Box 4, Folders 21-23; Box 20, Folders 11, 25) (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Norfolk--Jessie Townsend personal papers, notes drafts (folder 2 of 2) (see also Box 4, Folders 21-23; Box 20, Folders 11, 25) (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Norfolk--miscellaneous papers (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Norfolk County (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Northampton County (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Northumberland County--Heathsville (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Nottoway County--Burkeville (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Orange County (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Patrick County--names1920 (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Patrick County--Stuart (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Petersburg (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Petersburg--lists, 1916, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Pittsylvania County, 1917 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Portsmouth, 1914-1916, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Prince Edward County--Farmville, 1914-1917, undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Prince George County (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Prince William County--Manassas (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Princess Anne County (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Pulaski County (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Rappahannock County (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Richmond--history, list of officers, 1910-1917 (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Richmond--officers, 1912, 1917, 1919, undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Richmond--executive board meeting minutes, 1912-1913 (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Richmond--executive council minutes, 1918-1919 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Richmond--annual reports to Richmond league, 1911-1918 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Richmond--annual reports for conventions, 1914, 1916-1917 (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Richmond--headquarters secretary reports, 1914 (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Richmond--executive secretary reports, 1917-1920 (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Richmond--Resolutions (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Richmond--membership (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Richmond--membership list, 1913 (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Richmond--membership lists, undated (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - Richmond--membership lists by ward, undated (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Richmond--pledge cards, 1915-1919, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Richmond--canvass, undated (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Richmond--philanthropic work by members, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Richmond--programs, 1912-1914 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Richmond--essay contest, 1912 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Richmond--Lila Meade Valentine address, 7 January 1919 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Richmond--Madison Ward precinct maps (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Richmond--Equal Suffrage Auxiliary Red Cross, 1917 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Richmond--list of board of aldermen, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Richmond--miscellaneous papers (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Richmond--stationery (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Richmond County (Box 15, Folder 10)